{
    "results": [
        {
            "question": "Commonly used data types DO NOT include:",
            "correct_answer": "alerts",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "strings",
                "booleans",
                "numbers"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The condition in an if-statement is enclosed within...",
            "correct_answer": "parentheses",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "quotes",
                "curly brackets",
                "square brackets"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store _____.",
            "correct_answer": "All of the Above",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Numbers and Strings",
                "Other aarrays",
                "booleans"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the console is:",
            "correct_answer": "console.log()",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "JavaScript",
                "terminal",
                "for-loops"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "JQuery is the same thing as JQueryUI",
            "correct_answer": "No, geez!",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Yes",
                "Ask again later",
                "What is JQuery?"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which software company developed JavaScript?",
            "correct_answer": "Netscape",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mozilla",
                "Sun Microsystems",
                "Oracle"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Look at the following selector: $(‘div’). What does it select?",
            "correct_answer": "All div elements",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The first div element",
                "The last div element",
                "Current div element"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How can a value be appended to an array?",
            "correct_answer": "arr[arr.length]=value;",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "arr(length).value;",
                "arr[]=add(value);",
                "None of these"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What will the code below output to the console? console.log(1 +  +‘2’ + ‘2’);",
            "correct_answer": "console.log()",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "JavaScript",
                "terminal",
                "for-loops"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What will this output? var a = [1, 2, 3]; console.log(a[6]);",
            "correct_answer": "undefined",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "0",
                "prints nothing",
                "Syntax error"
            ]
        }        
    ]
}